[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "How do you think things have played out since we last spoke?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "things", "have", "played", "out", "since", "we", "last", "spoke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I feel a lot better tonight than I did after South Carolina, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "a", "lot", "better", "tonight", "than", "I", "did", "after", "South", "Carolina", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Was that the kind of Mitt Romney you've been looking for?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "the", "kind", "of", "Mitt", "Romney", "you", "'ve", "been", "looking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Well, I'm a big fan of Mitt Romney, not because of his combativeness, but because of his intellect and his ability to persuade all kinds of people to get together and get the right answers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "not", "because", "of", "his", "combativeness", ",", "but", "because", "of", "his", "intellect", "and", "his", "ability", "to", "persuade", "all", "kinds", "of", "people", "to", "get", "together", "and", "get", "the", "right", "answers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "But what does that tell you about the way his campaign is now going?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "way", "his", "campaign", "is", "now", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I think that Newt is going to go all the way to the end, the way he says he's going to go all the way to the end.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "Newt", "is", "going", "to", "go", "all", "the", "way", "to", "the", "end", ",", "the", "way", "he", "says", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "go", "all", "the", "way", "to", "the", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "And we're already seeing him developing into a much more formidable opponent, I would argue, from the debates last week than he may have been if he'd won South Carolina and already won the nomination?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "'re", "already", "seeing", "him", "developing", "into", "a", "much", "more", "formidable", "opponent", ",", "I", "would", "argue", ",", "from", "the", "debates", "last", "week", "than", "he", "may", "have", "been", "if", "he", "'d", "won", "South", "Carolina", "and", "already", "won", "the", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Look, Mitt Romney's big issue is connecting, is being comfortable in his own skin, is to let people know who he really is.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "big", "issue", "is", "connecting", ",", "is", "being", "comfortable", "in", "his", "own", "skin", ",", "is", "to", "let", "people", "know", "who", "he", "really", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "That's the American way, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "American", "way", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Finally, he did it.", "answer_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "he", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "It's all good fodder for the opposition as well, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "good", "fodder", "for", "the", "opposition", "as", "well", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, look, that's what's always said in the primary, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "always", "said", "in", "the", "primary", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And Jack, what is the truth about the state of the American economy right now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Jack", ",", "what", "is", "the", "truth", "about", "the", "state", "of", "the", "American", "economy", "right", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, we have a very tepid recovery, but we do have a recovery.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "a", "very", "tepid", "recovery", ",", "but", "we", "do", "have", "a", "recovery", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 236, "question": "What about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "It's not all --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "all", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "So what you're basically saying, Suzy, is that Mitt Romney's inability to sing could become an electoral positive for him?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "you", "'re", "basically", "saying", ",", "Suzy", ",", "is", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "inability", "to", "sing", "could", "become", "an", "electoral", "positive", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Suzy", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Why should do you feel that he should pull out?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "should", "pull", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Piers, let's get this straight.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "let", "'s", "get", "this", "straight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Is it good for the party if Rick Santorum and Ron Paul continue to the bitter end or should one of them take one for the team fairly soon?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "good", "for", "the", "party", "if", "Rick", "Santorum", "and", "Ron", "Paul", "continue", "to", "the", "bitter", "end", "or", "should", "one", "of", "them", "take", "one", "for", "the", "team", "fairly", "soon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I think it's good if they end up being strong supporters and believers in whoever the winning candidate is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "good", "if", "they", "end", "up", "being", "strong", "supporters", "and", "believers", "in", "whoever", "the", "winning", "candidate", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Ron Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How did you come across this extra bit of a tape?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "come", "across", "this", "extra", "bit", "of", "a", "tape", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "We felt the same way.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "felt", "the", "same", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "And this actually the box you found the tape in, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "actually", "the", "box", "you", "found", "the", "tape", "in", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "This is the box and the tape is in it.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "box", "and", "the", "tape", "is", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Douglas Brinkley"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "You know, how did we get from A to B?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "how", "did", "we", "get", "from", "A", "to", "B", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Let me go to Douglas Brinkley here.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "go", "to", "Douglas", "Brinkley", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "How significant, do you think, these tapes are in terms of suddenly surfacing like this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "these", "tapes", "are", "in", "terms", "of", "suddenly", "surfacing", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, it's a fascinating story.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "fascinating", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "What does that tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "What is the worth, Douglas, would you say, from an historical important point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "worth", ",", "Douglas", ",", "would", "you", "say", ",", "from", "an", "historical", "important", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, you can't write about the Kennedy assassination without grappling with the contents of this tape, meaning the information that's now available on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "write", "about", "the", "Kennedy", "assassination", "without", "grappling", "with", "the", "contents", "of", "this", "tape", ",", "meaning", "the", "information", "that", "'s", "now", "available", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Douglas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "How do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I just saw it on your show.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "saw", "it", "on", "your", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "How do you know he wasn't told to hide it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "he", "was", "n't", "told", "to", "hide", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Because it wouldn't just be in somebody's box in their estate.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "would", "n't", "just", "be", "in", "somebody", "'s", "box", "in", "their", "estate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Do you believe in any conspiracy theories?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "any", "conspiracy", "theories", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "None of them?", "question_tokens": ["None", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I think it's fun to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "fun", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Isn't it, all the Republican race?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", ",", "all", "the", "Republican", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "The truth for me is I'm always marketing.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "truth", "for", "me", "is", "I", "'m", "always", "marketing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do you talk about it on your stand-up?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "talk", "about", "it", "on", "your", "stand-up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Wasn't -- you mean, years ago, they couldn't say Peter?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "--", "you", "mean", ",", "years", "ago", ",", "they", "could", "n't", "say", "Peter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Why is that Peter?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "Peter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Why are you called Howie?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "called", "Howie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "That's old English for Ned.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "old", "English", "for", "Ned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "So here is a guy who has one of the world's most infamous germaphobias, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "here", "is", "a", "guy", "who", "has", "one", "of", "the", "world", "'s", "most", "infamous", "germaphobias", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Let me -- can I set the record straight?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "--", "can", "I", "set", "the", "record", "straight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "You can try.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Do you know who he is?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "who", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "He wouldn't get past first go, would he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "would", "n't", "get", "past", "first", "go", ",", "would", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "But it's great television because it's awkward and uncomfortable.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "great", "television", "because", "it", "'s", "awkward", "and", "uncomfortable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "How are you feeling about Howard Stern replacing me?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "about", "Howard", "Stern", "replacing", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "You know what, I'll be totally honest, I loved working with you much more than you loved working with me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "'ll", "be", "totally", "honest", ",", "I", "loved", "working", "with", "you", "much", "more", "than", "you", "loved", "working", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Howard Stern"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Would you like him to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "No, I don't think that's our job.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "'s", "our", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "How many followers do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "followers", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "I don't have a lot of followers, because I can't plug -- @HowieMMandel.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "followers", ",", "because", "I", "ca", "n't", "plug", "--", "@", "HowieMMandel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Why would anybody want to follow you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "anybody", "want", "to", "follow", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Because I'm wonderfully entertaining.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "wonderfully", "entertaining", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Who told you about twitter?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "told", "you", "about", "twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "You told me to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "told", "me", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Is that why you called me here today?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "why", "you", "called", "me", "here", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I would like you to apologize.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "you", "to", "apologize", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "For being me?", "question_tokens": ["For", "being", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Say sorry for being so annoying.", "answer_tokens": ["Say", "sorry", "for", "being", "so", "annoying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "But what happens to the 30 million people without jobs?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "happens", "to", "the", "30", "million", "people", "without", "jobs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "We have to -- and this is -- I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "to", "--", "and", "this", "is", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "You can do serious.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "serious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]